Dong Yeon Nam

Department of systems Biomedical Science School Soongsil University

PERSONAL DATA

Brith: 18th Jul 1996, in Republic of South Korea

Nationality: Korean Gender: Male Military Service: Yes

Email: dongyeon718@gmail.com

PERSONAL INFORMATION

I am a graduate student in Department of Systems Biomedical Science, Soongsil University. While attending undergraduate classes and working as a research intern, I became interested next-generation sequencing (NGS), Bio Artificial Intelligence and Machine Learning. And I am currently working as a researcher at Biomedical Data Science Laboratory Soongsil University

EDUCATION

Mar. 2015 ~ Soongsil University Seoul, Korea

Feb. 2022 Department of Systems Biomedical Science

Graduate student (Bachelor of Science)

B.S., Major: Bioinformatics and Biotechnology

Advisor: Prof. Je-Keun Rhee

Sep. 2022 ~ Soongsil University Seoul, Korea

Present Bioinformatics

Undergraduate student (Master of Science)

M.S., Major: Bioinformatics Advisor: Prof. Je-Keun Rhee

RESEARCH INTEREST

- ✓ Bio Artificial Intelligence
- ✓ Next Generation Sequencing (NGS)

RESEARCH EXPERIENCES

• Undergraduate Research Assistant Mar. 2021 ~ Feb. 2022

- ✓ at Biomedical Data Science Laboratory, Soongsil University
- ✓ Advisor: Prof. Je-Keun Rhee
- **Researcher** Mar. 2022 ~ Aug. 2022
- ✓ at Biomedical Data Science Laboratory, Soongsil University
- ✓ Advisor: Prof. Je-Keun Rhee

SKILLS AND TECHNIQUES

- Software Language
 - ✓ R, Python
- Computer Skill
 - ✓ Linux

AWARDS

• This Year's Natural Science Research Encouragement Award

Dec 9 (Fri), 2022

College of Natural Sciences, Soongsil University

PUBLICATIONS

1. **Dong-Yeon Nam, Je-Keun Rhee**, Assessment of MicroRNAs Associated with Tumor Purity by Random Forest Regression, *Biology*, 11:787, 2022.

PROJECT

PERSONAL PROJECT

Genome-Wide association study identifies genetic susceptibility loci about DNA repair activated by oxidative stress. (Practice of Biostatistics, 2020)

CNN (Separable Conv2D) for identifying Invasive Ductal Carcinoma. (Bio Artificial Intelligence, 2021)

TEAM PROJECT

Development of next-generation genomic application technology for 4D-nucleome-based cardiomyopathy. (Sep.2022 - Present)

WORKSHOP \$ CONFERENCE

• 16th Asian Institute in Statistical Genetics and Genomics Workshop

July 18 (Mon) - 23 (Sat), 2022

Seoul National University, Global Education Center for Engineers

• 2022 Annual Conference of Korean Society for Bioinformatics

October 19 (Wed) - 21 (Fri), 2022

KAIST, Daejeon, Korea

The 19th KOGO Winter Symposium

February 01 (Wed) - 03 (Fri), 2023

Vivaldi Park, Hongcheon-gun, Gangwon-do, Korea.